2025-05-23 - resize badge icon
2025-05-23 - minor styling
2025-05-23 - feat: cascade recipe, add missing field on history scan controller
2025-05-23 - give the premium and credit state from side bar'
2025-05-23 - change api url
2025-05-23 - feat: add controller and routes for every page fetching
2025-05-23 - check group items on ingridients
2025-05-23 - match variable from page visit
2025-05-23 - import missing dependency
2025-05-23 - fetch from pages visit
2025-05-23 - fetch from pages visit
2025-05-23 - fetch from pages visit
2025-05-22 - minor styling
2025-05-22 - minor fix
2025-05-22 - minor style
2025-05-22 - remove unecessary log
2025-05-22 - display tooltip about user credit
2025-05-22 - feat: add reduce credit middleware
2025-05-22 - fetch reducecredit
2025-05-22 - remove cache if user leave results page
2025-05-22 - cache food scan, check credit and user premium status
2025-05-22 - add camera comp, still not efficient ill fix it later
2025-05-22 - add more credit to new user
2025-05-21 - feat: add 404 page
2025-05-21 - fix(style): tweak layout for desktop preview
2025-05-20 - guard sign in button on token request and add spin animation
2025-05-20 - fix: add the email parameter on requestResetToken
2025-05-20 - add limiter for token request
2025-05-20 - separate requestToken as a utility
2025-05-20 - fix(name): fix spelling
2025-05-20 - feat: add reset password related router
2025-05-20 - feat: add resetpassword notification page  and its functionality
2025-05-20 - feat: add resetpassword page (re-use emailVerification) and its functionality
2025-05-20 - add: request token function and redirect to the notification page
2025-05-20 - add: request token function and redirect to the notification page
2025-05-20 - feat: template to sent the url for the password reset
2025-05-20 - add reset token functionality, create token, check token, and change password
2025-05-20 - feat: add reset password token table
2025-05-20 - return null password as an incorect password error
2025-05-20 - format current date display
2025-05-20 - show foodcontent on home
2025-05-19 - change bg color
2025-05-19 - change url redirection on login success
2025-05-19 - change api url
2025-05-19 - fix: on sign up password validation fail
2025-05-19 - minor graph styling
2025-05-19 - auto login everytime user created
2025-05-19 - request code then redirect to verification page
2025-05-19 - feat(auth): add code verification page
2025-05-19 - feat: add nodemailer utility to send the verification code
2025-05-19 - feat(auth): add verification code for every user creation with email
2025-05-19 - feat: add LoginCode table
2025-05-19 - set passwordhas as optional to allow google oauth user creation, password has null handled on frontend
2025-05-19 - feat: add google oauth
2025-05-19 - return early after prediction
2025-05-19 - font size style
2025-05-19 - update css, trying to collapse url bar on mobile preview
2025-05-19 - minor style
2025-05-19 - minor styling
2025-05-18 - feat: add camera facing mode feature
2025-05-18 - add home routes for redirecting user
2025-05-18 - add frontend url on cors
2025-05-18 - update import naming
2025-05-18 - use backend end url to forward jtw cookie
2025-05-18 - fix(proxy): forward JWT cookie to flask model api via express proxy
2025-05-18 - update cookie rule
2025-05-18 - update dependency clash
2025-05-18 - update dir
2025-05-18 - move config dir
2025-05-18 - add start command
2025-05-18 - minor install, move dir
2025-05-18 - install cookie parser
2025-05-18 - move the limiter module, install express rate limit
2025-05-18 - feat: add routes limiter
2025-05-18 - add upgrade user setting
2025-05-18 - add delete account function later
2025-05-18 - prevent setLoading prematurely, dont runt the usedailytotals if profile content is not ready
2025-05-18 - feat: set isLoading to be true on sign in
2025-05-18 - prevent component flash on MyFood page
2025-05-18 - prevent component flashing
2025-05-17 - minor update
2025-05-17 - feat: add authentication using jwt token
2025-05-17 - update icon dir
2025-05-17 - change use_auth_token to token, it will be deprecated
2025-05-17 - update port
2025-05-17 - update env
2025-05-17 - updated
2025-05-17 - update
2025-05-17 - commit req file
2025-05-17 - add update field controller and router
2025-05-17 - feat: add update field
2025-05-16 - update
2025-05-16 - return the new created scan
2025-05-16 - get the scan data from storescanandresut
2025-05-16 - feat: store api url into a single global variable
2025-05-16 - create notification components
2025-05-16 - feat: fetch recipe from backend
2025-05-16 - use state if exist, fetch if not
2025-05-16 - feat: add recipe controller and router, protect external api from express
2025-05-16 - add all the nutrition field for the user provider
2025-05-16 - redirect to the food details when user click the card
2025-05-16 - add all the fields for daily intake
2025-05-16 - feat: add update field pages
2025-05-16 - feat: add logout logic, redirect to update field when user click
2025-05-16 - separate layout
2025-05-16 - feat: add new layout
2025-05-16 - show animation when loading the data
2025-05-16 - show animation when loading the data
2025-05-16 - return more field from the dailyintakelogs
2025-05-16 - use dailyintake for calories, usesr profile scan for history
2025-05-16 - feat: add intakelog controller and router
2025-05-16 - feat: save every scan, save intake log
2025-05-16 - feat: include more recipe field
2025-05-16 - add food router
2025-05-16 - feat: add arial label
2025-05-16 - feat: add get recipe by id
2025-05-16 - feat: add scandetails route
2025-05-16 - redirect to scandetails when user clicking the food card
2025-05-16 - feat: add meta data
2025-05-16 - feat: add scan details for the food history
2025-05-15 - use user timezone
2025-05-15 - format utc into local time
2025-05-14 - show loading on scan fetching
2025-05-14 - feat: add additional fields for user
2025-05-14 - feat: style settings page
2025-05-14 - feat: handle food search from myfood page
2025-05-14 - feat: handle food search from home page
2025-05-14 - sort data from the oldes
2025-05-14 - feat: add recipe details routes
2025-05-14 - feat: add recipe details page, fetch the selected recipe
2025-05-14 - style recipe card
2025-05-13 - feat: add recipe page, fetch from food api
2025-05-13 - add parameter to the search bar
2025-05-12 - add filter, setfilter and name parameter
2025-05-12 - feat: add filter
2025-05-12 - feat: add calories line chart
2025-05-12 - feat: add calories line chart
2025-05-12 - feat: show food scan history, reuse the FoodContent components
2025-05-12 - feat: add scan history
2025-05-12 - change color gradient
2025-05-11 - user predifined color or by index
2025-05-11 - use shared component to show daily intake information
2025-05-11 - use shared component to show graph
2025-05-11 - use index
2025-05-11 - modularize NutrienInfoGraph
2025-05-11 - modularize FoodContent Card
2025-05-11 - feat: add utility to get user nutrient intake, cat by date
2025-05-11 - feat: add badgelookup back, use random color for new badges
2025-05-11 - feat: add calories page, reuse chart from home, display for every date
2025-05-11 - feat: add more nutrition progress bar
2025-05-10 - feat: calculate and display intake log for the day
2025-05-10 - remove badgelookup, use randomize color so all type of badges will be shown
2025-05-10 - add the multer upload
2025-05-10 - minor update
2025-05-10 - feat: add image upload on each controller
2025-05-10 - fix: fix the return message on form validation, provide it from the middleware
2025-05-10 - add id field on return
2025-05-10 - upload image on default openai prompt scan
2025-05-10 - feat: add createScan controller to save new scan
2025-05-10 - move user provider to parent routes
2025-05-10 - feat: add new gear icon
2025-05-10 - feat: add settings page
2025-05-10 - separate image compression to its own utility
2025-05-10 - feat: save scan history and  image on every scan
2025-05-10 - change more to settings on the navigation
2025-05-09 - feat: add calorie intake chart on home screen
2025-05-09 - protect openai api with auth
2025-05-09 - feat: add sign up functionality
2025-05-08 - feat: add router protection on the parent layout
2025-05-08 - protect profile provider with the authenticate token
2025-05-08 - feat: add user profile provider, get user data for the frontend app
2025-05-08 - feat: add signUp and signIn pages, configure the signup logic
2025-05-08 - update user check on sign up
2025-05-08 - feat: configure jwt login with httpOnly cookie
2025-05-08 - feat: add passport configuration and auth middleware
2025-05-08 - feat: add onboarding page
2025-05-07 - minor fix on open ai vision model
2025-05-06 - comment dropdown for model selection
2025-05-06 - feat: add nutrient name normalizer, so any naming case will match by regex
2025-05-06 - update scraper
2025-05-06 - update folder
2025-05-06 - feat: add snakecase text formatter
2025-05-06 - feat: handle openai and db fetching, separate normal and premium user analysis model, create new visionFetching for the premium user
2025-05-06 - feat: separate result.js component into smaller managable components
2025-05-06 - feat: configure multer
2025-05-06 - feat: configure cloudinary storage
2025-05-06 - feat: handle openai vision, configure multer and cloudinary,  store uploaded image into cloudinary
2025-05-06 - feat: add getAllRecipeName router
2025-05-06 - feat: add dummy user
2025-05-06 - feat: add openai image vision to analyze the captured image for the premium user
2025-05-06 - feat: upsert new recipe
2025-05-05 - feat: udpdate todo
2025-05-05 - feat: finsih result page styling, fetch predicted result, create skeleton element
2025-05-05 - feat: basic crud for food data, fetch food information from open ai
2025-05-05 - feat: create orm model
2025-05-05 - feat: add dummy field and style the result page
2025-05-04 - feat: style result page, create utility function
2025-05-04 - feat: prevent bottom nav to get pushed by the url bar on mobile preview
2025-05-04 - feat: update todo
2025-05-04 - feat: separate svg icon, show predicted result in new page
2025-05-04 - feat: setup openai router and controller
2025-05-04 - feat: setup CORS for flask api
2025-05-04 - feat: scrap homepage trending recipe url, scrape all the information for each url that have been scraped before, todo: make it one into one process
2025-05-04 - feat: format scraped data
2025-05-03 - feat: mvp, working camera, upload, and prediciton
2025-05-03 - feat: style home components
2025-05-02 - feat: style home pages
2025-05-02 - feat: bottom navigation, basic home layout
2025-05-02 - update ipynb file
2025-05-02 - initial: vite react app initialization
2025-05-02 - intial: express app initialization
2025-05-01 - add missing import
2025-05-01 - feat: initialize flask api for basic prediction
2025-05-01 - feat: load pre trained model
2025-05-01 - feat: load pre trained model
